People talk a lot
about what it means to be
a member of a team.
♪ As soon as I get my head
around you ♪
Shred. shred!
♪ I come around
Catching sparks off you
♪ I get an electric charge
from you ♪
Thanks. man.
The brotherhood.
the sense of belonging
to something greater
than yourself.
Set. go!
Hold the ball!
Hey. it's going right.
it's going right!
Throwing right. throwing right.
♪ Makes you wanna feel
Makes you wanna try
♪ Makes you wanna blow
The stars from the sky
♪ I can't stand up
I can't cool down
♪ I can't get my head
Off the ground ♪
It's about
fighting together.
but it's also about family.
About knowing
who will be there
for you. always.
♪ As soon as I get my head
Around you
♪ I come around
Catching sparks off you
♪ And all I ever
got from you
Was all I ever... ♪
And when it's right.
when it's 11 guys
working as one.
there's nothing like it.
Set. go!
♪ The world
could die in pain
♪ And I wouldn't feel
no shame
♪ And there's nothing
Holding me to blame
♪ Makes you wanna feel
Makes you wanna try
♪ Makes you wanna blow
The stars from the sky
♪ And I'm taking myself
To a dirty part of town
♪ Where all my troubles
Can't be found ♪
No greater feeling in the world.
Fuck me. you're heavy.
Hey!
Yeah. man. no wonder Westfield
couldn't tackle your ass.
Fuck you. guys.
My fat ass saved
yours. butterfingers.
Hey!
Ouch!
Lucky I was doubled up
all night or else you
wouldn't have gotten shit.
And I thank you.
Dude. that catch? Insane!
You're so getting your
dick sucked tonight!
Hey. Monty. you wanna do
the honors?
You know what? I would.
That's how amazing
that catch was.
Party at your place. Walker?
No.
His parents are in town.
We're hitting the docks.
See you. guys.
See ya.
Great game. Bryce!
Thanks. Mr. Dempsey.
Looking for someone?
No. I. um...
I was just... No.
I'm Hannah.
We met at Kat's party.
Yes. Yeah. no. I remembered.
I... I was just...
It's cool. Yeah.
Probably all those concussions
out there. right?
Yeah. something like that.
Didn't know
you were a football fan.
My mom made me come.
Oh. okay. okay.
Yeah. She said it'd be
good for me to meet people.
make some friends.
And now she's off somewhere
making friends for herself.
and here I am.
Well. at least she's here.
Mine are apparently
still in Zurich or wherever
the hell it is this week.
Can your parents take mine
with them sometime?
Yeah. Absolutely.
I'll talk to them about that.
Good game. man.
I. uh... I should go
find my mother.
Sure. Sure.
Hey. friend.
Let's hang out sometime.
Maybe that's why
Hannah pursued me.
because she had
never felt that...
That sense of belonging.
Aren't the glasses a bit much?
Yeah. I haven't worn these
in. like. forever.
Warren thinks
they make him look
more empathetic. relatable.
And can't he
just be those things?
Look. Warren is
the best there is
at reading a jury.
Our family's on trial today.
You shouldn't even be in that
room. for Christ's sake.
We could've fought off
a bullshit subpoena
for a rinky-dink lawsuit.
I got this. I spent.
like. four hours
with Warren and his guys.
- We're good.
- Are we good?
The reporters out front
didn't seem to think so.
Enough.
The kid doesn't need
any more static.
If she doesn't know
this happened to her.
she's gonna be destroyed.
And once she does.
I'm not gonna be the one
who tells her that the whole
world needs to know. too.
They're gonna have
to take down Bryce
without her.
- He's just going to lie.
- Maybe.
But you go up there thinking
you'll know what to say.
and then it ends up going
another way completely.
you know?
Yeah. which is how I know
we can't count on them
to get Bryce.
Look. if we don't stop this.
there will be more Chloes...
And Bryces...
And Ninas.
Oh. my God.
This is proof. Jessica.
Proof of who Bryce is.
who they all are.
Proof that you're not alone.
And that makes it easier?
What. like we're some part
of a fucking club?
Jesus. you guys...
Wait. we...
That might be evidence.
Well. it doesn't belong to you.
Aren't you pissed off?
I've made a lot of enemies
in this town.
It's Bryce.
You think so?
Yes.
No. he wouldn't get his hands
dirty with this.
But who else would it be?
Bryce has money.
And boys like him.
men like him. they have
protectors and enablers
and people with lots to lose
if they're found out.
Can I come to court
with you today?
Okay.
Why are you in this picture?
I'm sure I can't tell you
anything worse than
what you're imagining.
I don't know.
So far. things have been worse
than I ever would've imagined.
What do you want me
to say. Clay?
Would you believe
nothing happened?
How did you end up
in the Clubhouse? I mean.
whose jacket is it?
You know I dated Justin.
He said he didn't know
about the Clubhouse.
And you believe him?
I don't know. I...
So. what do you wanna hear?
That I dated
half the baseball team?
That they got me high
and fucked me blind?
I...
I wanna know the truth.
I told you my truth.
but you don't believe me.
You say you love me.
but you're always willing
to believe the worst of me.
Clay Jensen
has the rest. They're safe.
I know how much you talk about
your story being yours. so...
I thought you should get to
decide what to do with this.
Yeah. but the thing is
is that this isn't my story.
This is the lie.
That I was into it
and having fun. you know?
And I guess I was. you know.
until...
But there's no picture
of that. is there?
No proof.
You know. maybe if
there was. maybe...
Maybe I'd be dealing with my
shit a little better. right?
Nina. I am so sorry
that I said that stuff
to you yesterday. honestly.
You were right. though.
I...
I cheated on Garrett
with Michael.
And when you called me out...
I didn't mean to call you out.
No. but you should have.
I wanted to be strong for you...
To be what you needed.
but I'm not.
And I don't think
that I ever will be.
Maybe we're just gonna never
stop being victims.
You said that Hannah
pursued you
after that football game
at the beginning
of your junior year.
Did it ever turn physical?
Yes. We had kind of
an on-again.
off-again thing.
So... You had sex
more than once?
We did.
So. Hannah
initiated this
"on-again. off-again thing"?
Yes. she did.
She took me
to Hickman's Bridge...
Which. honestly.
I remember thinking
was kind of creepy.
I like the idea
that somebody built this thing
that holds people up.
helps them get
where they need to go.
And yet. one wrong turn...
And you're plummeting
down. down. down. splat.
Game over.
Did you take me out here
to murder me?
No. I just...
You know. we take it for
granted. life and. like.
how precarious it is.
I don't know. coming here.
it helps me step out
of mine sometimes.
Yeah.
And to remember
how precious life is.
Exactly.
How do you mean "it was creepy"?
Well. just the whole bridge
thing. Being obsessed
with a place like that.
I just wish I had realized
it might have been a sign.
And how many times
did you go
to Hickman's Bridge?
Gosh. I don't know.
Um. quite a few.
I guess it kind of
became our place.
And what did you do there?
Sometimes we just made
out. um. looked at the stars.
Sometimes we made love.
Are you sure you want to?
I'm sure.
Did things ever evolve
into a committed relationship?
Not really.
Did you want it to?
Um. I had a great time
with Hannah.
but she wasn't really
girlfriend material.
Hannah had a reputation.
And she didn't deserve it
at all. but you know
how kids are.
I was too ashamed
to admit that I was
having sex with her.
And how did Hannah
feel about that?
I think she wanted more.
She would always hang around
after football games.
after baseball practice...
Isn't it. like. freedom.
being on your own. though?
I mean. I think
your life sounds amazing.
Yeah. yeah. it mostly is.
That looks good on you.
Let me get a picture.
Oh. no way. No photos.
Come on! You're so beautiful.
I would probably
hide the pipe. though.
You don't want people to think
you're a complete stoner.
All right.
So beautiful.
Unh-unh.
Oh. God. no!
I don't want to see it.
What?
I don't want to look
at myself.
Seriously?
Because I could look at you
forever.
♪ High
♪ Over the north star
Sleepless. so far
♪ Together. we are high
♪ Trapped in
the holiday affair
♪ A new silence
filled the air
♪ I rest my head
on your shoulder
♪ There's nowhere else
I'd rather be
♪ Right there.
a little bit slower
I wanted to be with him forever.
I was in love with him.
Bryce. you said
that Hannah wanted
a more serious relationship.
yes?
Yes.
- Did she tell you so?
- She did.
When?
The night of my party.
And that was the party
on September 30th?
Correct.
And what made you think
that Hannah wanted
something more serious?
Because she told me so.
After we had sex.
she said that she wanted
to be exclusive.
And I said. you know.
"I like you. but as a friend."
So. how do you
explain Hannah's report
that you did something to her
at that party?
She lied to Mr. Porter.
Why would she do that?
Because she was hurt
and angry.
I... I get that.
I tried to let her down gently.
Hannah really was
a fantastic girl.
but. look. she let
her emotions
carry her away. right?
In high school. it's emotional.
What if Marcus calls your dad.
too. huh?
We have to get him back.
you know?
I'm trying to look out
for you. okay?
What about my sister?
I told you. I'm sorry
about everything...
Hey. Tyler.
You wanna go
to a movie sometime?
Thank you very much.
Mr. Wentworth.
Here you go.
Thank you. Paxton.
Thank you very much.
I was surprised
to see you in class.
Oh. yeah. I. uh. figured my
education was more important
than sitting around
a courtroom. you know.
'Course.
Plus. can't play ball
without that average. right?
Uh. listen. Coach. I...
Look. you had
a disagreement. okay?
It happens.
Sometimes brothers fight.
But that doesn't mean
they're not still your family.
Those guys aren't my family.
Well. what about me?
Wasn't I there for you
when you came to me
last summer?
Yeah.
Didn't we figure that out
together?
How to be strong for your
family. your mom?
Little May?
Zach. you think
you can be there
for your team
and for me... Now?
You don't get to do that. okay?
Just because you were there.
you think you can...
You know. if you were
any kind of father.
to this team or to anyone.
you would've stopped
their bullshit years ago.
That means I quit.
Bryce. you've gotten physical
with other classmates
against their wishes.
haven't you?
Uh. not that I remember. no.
Not Tyler Down?
Isn't it true that you
threw Tyler Down
up against a locker?
Oh. maybe.
but that's just guys
messing around.
He...
He knew I was joking.
So you think Tyler thought
you were messing around?
Objection.
Withdrawn.
Bryce. let's talk about this
party that you mentioned.
It was on September 30th
of last year. right?
Correct.
It was a Saturday?
Yes.
It was a nice night?
Lots of stars. full moon?
Yeah.
And your parents
were out of town?
Yes.
And you were celebrating
a big football win
from the night before. right?
We were celebrating
a loss. actually.
Uh...
We don't win all that often.
You were celebrating
a loss. and maybe people
had a drink or two?
Yes.
Maybe three or four?
Sure.
And Hannah Baker was there?
Yes.
And she was somebody
that you knew well.
but who you
weren't dating. right?
Right.
And Hannah got in
the hot tub with you?
Yes.
And everybody else got out
of the hot tub?
Yes.
And you started
to make out with her?
Yeah.
And you wanted to have sex
with her. right?
Yes.
And you got really into it?
Sure.
And you assumed
that she was into it. too.
correct?
Yes.
So. you turned her around
to take her from behind.
right?
Yes.
You pulled down
her underwear. right?
Yes.
And you took your own suit off
as well. correct?
- Yes.
- And. Bryce.
you usually use protection.
don't you?
Uh. I do. usually.
But you didn't use
protection with her
on that night. correct?
Correct.
And you two
didn't talk about STDs
or pregnancies. right?
We did not. no.
And she never did
actually say. "I want
to have sex with you."
isn't that correct?
Correct.
And she didn't make
any specific gestures
to indicate consent.
isn't that correct?
What. like... A thumbs-up?
Did she give you a thumbs-up?
She did not.
Then you had sex with her
against her will.
isn't that correct?
No. No. that is not correct.
She came on to me.
She came on to you.
but she never said she
wanted to have sex with you.
isn't that correct?
She clearly wanted
to hook up.
But she never gave you her
consent. isn't that right?
I... I knew what she wanted.
You knew what she wanted.
and yet when she went
to the school counselor
and reported that
she had been assaulted.
that was a lie?
Correct.
Why would she lie?
Objection.
Calls for speculation.
I'll rephrase. Was there
anything in your encounter
that would have led Hannah
to report that she
had been raped?
I... I wish I knew.
I would never do that
to any girl.
When I think about my mom
or my girlfriend...
Guys. Chloe took off.
I would
never want anyone
to hurt them.
And I never hurt Hannah.
But I saw it.
- Oh.
- Ah!
He lies through
his fucking teeth and
everybody shakes his hand.
Are we sure he lied?
Jesus. Clay. come on.
Those fucking glasses?
We can't tell Jessica
about any of this.
We have to tell Jessica.
We need Chloe.
Hey. Kevin.
Coach.
Listen. Have you been talking
to Zach Dempsey?
No. not lately. Why?
He's talking about
quitting the team because
of this thing with Bryce.
Mmm-hmm. "This thing."
- You mean that Bryce is a rapist.
- Okay.
Kev. come on. Innocent until
proven guilty. huh?
So. you think he's innocent?
I think he is.
I think that
this is a witch hunt.
A troubled girl took her own
life. and we want to blame.
but it's not that simple.
I would hate to see
someone's future
be ruined because of it.
I would've thought
you of all people
would appreciate that. Kev.
No one wants a record.
No. No. you're right.
No one wants to be
on the wrong side of the law.
What do you want?
I heard you walked out
of court today...
While Bryce was on the stand.
Look. I know
you're the one who
crossed out all that bullshit
about me in the stall.
Why?
Because you were on the squad.
I wanted to protect you.
I had already quit by then.
Do you remember
going to a place
called the Clubhouse?
This is gonna be hard
to look at. okay?
Do you remember this happening?
Chloe.
You don't remember. do you?
Why would he do this?
Because... Because
he's a bad guy.
He's sick.
He's done this to me and you
and who knows who else.
And he takes pictures.
or. in my case. puts them up
on a whiteboard at school.
Oh. God. Jess.
What?
I never...
I... I thought those pictures
would scare you
into not calling Bryce out
in court.
Wait. you put them up?
I'm so sorry.
What else have you done?
It was just the pictures.
I just...
I wanted to believe
the rumors about you
were true.
God. he fucking lied to me.
Do you wanna
do something about it?
What if it's true?
Jesus. what if it's true?
How could you possibly
believe it's true?
The stuff about Zach was true.
Zach's a good person.
Deep down. he's a lot like you.
Oh. God. don't say shit
like that.
Zach's just like
the rest of them.
Zach. and Montgomery.
and Scott. and Bryce.
And Justin?
Justin let him rape Jessica.
Justin would give his life
to do that over.
He should.
He should give his life.
He's your friend.
He's not my friend.
I was your friend.
So tell me he was lying.
Tell me Bryce was lying
about everything... Now.
Jesus. Hannah.
tell me he was lying!
He told lies.
It was all lies. All of it.
Don't think about it. Clay.
Just think about me.
Think about touching me.
Think about hugging me.
How it felt
when we were close.
No. no! Stop it.
I don't ever want
to think about that again.
Okay. Fine.
Just tell me what's true.
I need to know the truth.
Here we are. Tape 12.
If you've listened this far
and you haven't heard
your name yet.
well. I bet you know
exactly what's coming now.
Or maybe
you don't have any idea.
No.
No! Damn it. no!
Shut up!
Could that be true?
Please don't do this!
Leave me alone.
Can a person be that sick?
Let's find out.
Leave me alone!
Clay.
Clay. what... What is it?
I can't.
I can't do this.
Clay. listen.
Jess talked to Chloe.
She's gonna meet
with the lawyers.
We're gonna get him.
Chloe. Mrs. Rice.
our window is closing here.
To be clear. testifying
that Bryce raped you
on campus.
you'd help support
the argument that Liberty's
protection of rapists
allowed more rapes to happen
and refute Bryce's testimony
that he had consensual sex
with Hannah.
Do you understand?
I... I think so.
You mentioned.
uh. your little sister?
Amelia.
If you decide to testify
in that courtroom.
maybe the next girl.
maybe even Amelia will be safer.
Chloe. I know
this is a lot. We know it.
And I know
I'm asking you to do
the thing that I couldn't do.
that Hannah couldn't do.
But if you could do this
for all of us.
whatever happens next.
we have your back.
It's up to you. sweetheart.
It's whatever you decide.
Hey.
Listen. I told one friend.
I was... I mean. I was
just trying to figure out
what I did wrong...
So I told one friend.
and she's an asshole
and she told someone else.
and it just...
It got out of control.
I'm sorry.
Mack.
Cyrus. I'm talking to Tyler.
Come on.
The Coke machine
at the commons
is giving out doubles again.
Jesus.
I would love to end those
motherfuckers.
Right?
Then let's do it.
Nah. We wouldn't
want you to get
a bloody nose or anything.
I never thought
I'd be thanking
Clay Jensen for a ride.
Fuck me.
You're a goddamn liar.
This does not end well.
You never
hooked up with Hannah.
You would've told me.
Why? Because we
were best friends
and I told you everything?
I should kill you.
Hey. chill out.
Still gonna hide behind
your boys. Bryce?
I'm not hiding.
You wanna go?
Damn it.
I don't want to fight you.
Just breathe.
Faggot.
You fucking coward faggot.
Oh. yes!
Let's go. motherfuckers!
Yeah!
♪ Look at my face
See my pride
♪ Out of touch for a while
Get off! Get...
♪ In my place. I'm on trial
Get the fuck off!
♪ Spent too long in denial
♪ Now I don't get it
♪ Now
♪ Now I can't get it
♪ No. I don't get it
♪ Now
♪ No. I can't... ♪
What the fuck
is your problem. psycho?
You could've stopped it.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
That night at the party.
Hannah and Bryce.
Look. I didn't see anything
and neither did you.
Hannah's dead because of us.
Shut... Shut the fuck up.
You're gonna go to jail.
Guys. no.
Hey. stop!
Hey. hey! Guys! Hey. stop!
Boys! Hey!
What the fuck
are you pushing me for?
Take a fucking shot. man.
Come on!
Fucking boys.
Disgusting.
What?
Why didn't you hit me?
You look pretty bad already.
Which you helped with.
I didn't.
Bullshit.
I play baseball.
That doesn't make me
a fucking rapist.
Bryce Walker.
Can you come with us. please?
Mr. Jensen...
Just a minute. Coach.
No talking. no devices.
It's an emergency.
Chloe's testifying
for the Bakers.
Only you
could talk us
past Coach Patrick.
That man still loves you.
Yeah. I guess.
Oh. no.
- No. No. no. no!
- What is it?
Fuck.
Wait. the... The box.
The box. it's gone.
Jesus. you left them
in the fucking car?
What was I supposed to do?
Carry it around?
Put it in my locker?
It's child pornography.
for fuck's sake.
It's Bryce.
It had to be Bryce.
He was out ahead of us.
No. There's no way
he had any time.
And he was with that lawyer.
Well. maybe they both did it.
We are so fucked.
You lost them?
Jesus. keep your voice down.
What the fuck. Justin?
Bryce took them.
Look. we'll get them back.
How? How are we
gonna get them back?
It's in the woods.
behind the field.
It's this secret place that
you have to be invited to.
unless you're on
the baseball team.
And who invited you?
Bryce.
When you got
to the Clubhouse. do you
remember what happened next?
A little.
Just tell us what you can.
Um...
It's... It's kind of a blur.
We...
We listened to music.
And then... We. um.
we started drinking
and smoking pot.
So. do you remember
these photos being taken?
No.
So. you don't remember
having sex with Bryce Walker?
Um...
Chloe. you don't remember
having sex with Bryce Walker?
No. I...
I do. I remember.
You remember what?
We had sex.
But you... You don't
remember Bryce asking
for your consent. correct?
No. I... I do.
I remember that now.
We were drinking.
so I had forgotten. but...
But I wanted to.
Well. God fucking damn it.
I believed her.
I think she told us the truth
before she walked
into that courtroom.
They got to her.
Somehow they got to her.
I don't know.
It's just been a few hours.
and Warren's an ass.
but he's a good lawyer.
and he plays by the rules.
That family doesn't.
That boy doesn't.
And we just let him walk.
We can add them to the suit
if you want to.
Or file separately.
I'm sure they'd settle
before enduring another round
of headlines.
Oh. Dennis.
I don't want
Bryce Walker's money.
I want him dead.
♪ If you were to tell me
♪ If I'd have had to guess
♪ I never
would have told you
♪ If it is not a gift ♪
I was left alone in the hot tub.
♪ I will not forget it ♪
But not for long.
♪ As long as I live... ♪
Because that's when
you showed up. Bryce.
Please don't.
You got into the hot tub
and turned off the jets.
Please.
I tried.
We tried. Hannah.
Hey. You okay?
♪ Seems to be the wisdom ♪
I'm fine.
♪ Conventional regret
♪ Solitary protest
♪ There's nothing
to ingest ♪
It was all bullshit. wasn't it?
♪ I will not forget it
All that about taking back
the power.
♪ As long as I live...
Big fucking deal.
We can spray paint some shit.
they clean it up the next day.
♪ That I cannot forgive
Nothing does anything.
You wanna know what
real power feels like?
Oh!
Oh. my... This...
This feels fucking incredible.
Right? Told you.
♪ It's your time ♪
Shit.
You're really good.
Just takes practice.
You know what really helps.
though. is if you
name your targets.
Name them?
Yeah.
Like people you don't like
or whatever.
Kind of helps you focus.
You know. do it all in your
head. Watch.
Bryce Walker.
Fuck. yeah!
Shit.
Mr. Barbour must've called the
cops. Clay. we gotta go.
You turned me around
and pushed the full weight
of your body into my back.
- Clay. give me the gun.
- I couldn't move.
Clay.
I had no power.
Jesus. Clay. give me the gun.
Just run!
Oh. fuck.
Hmm.
This can't be the place. right?
It's the building that she
described.
Well...
No.
there were other Polaroids
of other girls.
There was proof.
You seem to be handling
everything very well.
Ah. pretty exhausting day.
I'm not gonna lie.
That was a...
That was a whole thing.
You know. your father
and I have always given you
a lot of freedom. Bryce.
We've always trusted that you
were responsible enough
to make good decisions.
Seems like it's worked out
pretty well so far.
I get to take care of myself.
you get to keep up
your tan year round.
Everybody wins. right?
What happened with Hannah?
You were there yesterday.
I don't think we heard
the whole story.
She came on to me.
We had sex.
I mean. I know you're aware
I'm sexually active.
You've known since
you walked in on me last year.
Turned and walked out
and never said anything
about it.
but you saw
a whole lot of naked.
And what happened with Chloe?
A whole lot of naked there. too.
Chloe's got problems. okay?
She comes from a broken home.
So. you had sex with her
when she was unconscious?
I didn't force her
to get drunk and stoned
at 4:00 in the afternoon.
Oh. just like you
didn't force Hannah to get
into the hot tub with you.
Why do you care?
You didn't even know Hannah.
Did you? Or was she just
another thing that you wanted?
You want to know what happened
with me and Hannah. Mom?
She got in the hot tub with me.
no suit. just panties
and a bra
over those very nice tits.
And she looked at me like.
like she was hungry.
And. yeah. I wanted her.
I just...
I just had to have her.
So. I took her.
I turned her around.
and I fucked her from behind.
Hard.
Until she cried.
Is that what you want to hear?
You've brought shame
on this family.
You're a stranger in this house.
Always have been. Mom.
Is Mrs. Baker
coming back tonight?
Nah. she's gone for the day.
Why don't you head home?
I'll lock up.
Okay.
Thanks.
Oh. there was a package
left for you earlier.
on the counter.
Who left it?
I don't know. Just showed up.
It wouldn't have
mattered if Chloe
came through today.
Don't you dare blame Chloe.
No. I know.
I'm just saying...
She wasn't ready.
She wasn't strong enough
to tell her story.
and that's not her fault.
I know.
If she says it out loud.
if she points at him and says.
"He did this."
her whole world
comes crashing down.
Hasn't your whole world
come crashing down?
I wish I could fix this. Jess.
I would do anything
to take everything
you've been through.
and put it on me.
You can't.
No. I can't.
But you can let me
point at him
and say. "He did this."
Justin. it's me again.
I'm gonna need you to bring my
car and meet me...
Meet me at the bottom of
Vaughan's Hill.
Um...
I got something I gotta do.
When I tried to climb out
of the hot tub.
you grabbed my arm.
You traced your fingers
down my bra strap
and over my bra.
I know. I know.
I'm taking care of it.
You pulled my underwear
down and used your body
to keep me trapped there.
I was frozen.
I was terrified.
Just... I remember. okay?
I remember.
♪ Unwillingly mine
♪ Fate
♪ Up against your will
♪ Through the thick and thin
♪ He will wait until
♪ You give yourself to him
♪ Fate
♪ Up against your will
♪ Through the thick and thin
♪ He will wait until
♪ You give yourself to him
♪ La
♪ La la la la
♪ La-la la la la
♪ La-la la-la
♪ La-la-la la la la
♪ Fate
♪ Up against your will
♪ Through the thick and thin
♪ He will wait until ♪
How are you
so fucking good at this?
It's a natural-born talent.
Montgomery.
And practice.
We've been playing
for. like. five hours.
What the fuck?
Jesus!
- I thought everyone went home.
- Yeah. me. too.
Who is it?
Just Bryce fucking
some chick in the hot tub.
Must be a desperate slut
at this hour.
Yeah.
You could've stopped it.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
That night at the party.
Hannah and Bryce.
Please. Bryce.
Hannah's dead because of us.
So. Hannah initiated this
"on-again. off-again thing"?
Yes. she did. She...
She took me
to Hickman's Bridge.
One wrong turn.
and you're plummeting down.
down. down.
Splat.
Game over.
Did you bring me here
to murder me?
No. No. I just...
I just mean we take it for
granted is all.
life and how precarious it is.
Coming here helps me
step out of mine sometimes.
I think I get it.
We should. uh...
We should get back.
Sometimes we
just made out. um.
looked at the stars.
Sometimes we made love.
Jeez. it's freezing in here.
Does this place
have any heat?
Oh. shit. Uh. no.
Sorry.
Here. take this.
Isn't it. like. freedom.
being on your own?
Yeah. I guess.
I got plenty of freedom. though.
It'd be nice to have them show
up every now and then.
That sounds kind of lonely.
Eh. sometimes. yeah.
I don't really
talk about this stuff
with a lot of people.
It's nice.
Yeah. it is.
That looks good on you.
Let me get a picture.
Oh. no way. No photos.
What?
Come on.
You're so beautiful.
Well. I probably
shouldn't pose with this.
Don't want everyone
to think the new girl
is a complete stoner.
So. your parents.
have you ever tried
to have. like. a real
conversation with them?
Let them know how you feel
about them being away
all the time and everything?
Whoa. Um...
What's the matter?
I thought we were
having a good time.
We are. It's just. um...
I like you. but as a friend.
Yeah. Okay. sure.
Oh. yeah.
Why were you
in the Clubhouse with him?
When I tried to climb
out of the hot tub.
you pulled me back in.
Tell me. or I'll ask him myself.
You told me
we were "just having fun."
I'll make him hurt.
I'll make him understand
what he did to you.
I struggled. but you were
too strong for me.
You pulled my underwear down
and used your body
to trap me there.
Clay. what are you doing?
Where did you get that?
You gripped my wrists
and pushed yourself
inside of me.
Get out of my way. Justin.
Come on. Clay.
this is fucking crazy.
It felt like a knife
cutting me open.
No one's gonna
get justice for her.
Hey. come on. Hey!
Move!
I begged you. "Please. Bryce."
but you told me to relax.
I talked to Jessica today.
She wants me to testify.
Bullshit. No. she doesn't.
Yes. I swear. she does.
You said you would
go "nice and easy." but you
went harder and faster.
So you'll just run away
or fucking overdose again?
Clay. come on.
When I cried out in pain.
you grabbed my hair
like the sound of my pain
made it better for you.
I can't count on anyone
else anymore. I have
to do this myself.
You don't have to do this
yourself. We can get him
tomorrow.
- I need to do it now.
- Why?
I just tried to leave my body.
I tried to forget
the anger and pain.
- For Hannah.
- Listen. Clay.
I know you loved her.
but she's gone.
And going in there
and hurting Bryce now
is not gonna bring her back.
She's gone.
If you're lucky.
you live a long life.
and one day. your body just
gives up. and it's over.
How do I make her stop?
She won't stop.
Make who stop?
The way I see it...
Who. Clay?
Who are you talking about?
- There are two kinds of death.
- Clay!
If you're not lucky.
you die a little bit...
Clay. come on.
Over and over.
until you realize it's too late.
Just stop.
Give me the gun.
What the fuck?
And in that moment. it felt...
It felt like I was already dead.
Well done. Ed.
Well done.